A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Civil War Commission, 1952-1966 (bulk 1958-1965)
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Subject Files, 1956-1966., Extent: 30.8 cu. ft. (Box 1-81d)
  - Projects.
    - Shenandoah Valley Circle Tour: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1965; undated. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Shenandoah Valley Circle Tour: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1965; undated. (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Shenandoah Valley Circle Tour: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1965; undated. (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Shenandoah Valley Circle Tour: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1965; undated. (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Tours: Correspondence, 1960-1963. (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Tours: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1963. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Heritage Month, 1961. (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Walter Dorwin Teague Plans, 1959. (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Walter Dorwin Teague Plans, 1959-1960. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Publications and Reference Material.
    - Library of Congress Publications.
      - Civil War Maps: An Annotated List, compiled by Richard W. Stephenson, 1961. (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - The American Civil War: A Centennial Exhibition, 1961. (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - The Civil War in Motion Pictures: A Bibliography of Films Produced in the United States since 1897, compiled by Paul C. Spehr, 1961. (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Articles, Pamphlets and Publications.
      - A Concise History of the Civil War, published by the Stackpole Company, 1961. (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Civil War Centennial, published by First and Merchants National Bank, 1958. (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Civil War Roundtable Guide, by James V. Murfin, undated. (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Civil War Songs, presented by the First United States Army Recruiting Service, 1960. (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Coast and Geodetic Survey, by the United States Department of Commerce, 1961. (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - Confederate Inflation Chart (Official Publication 13, Richmond Civil War Centennial Committee), undated. (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Confederate States Paper Money, by Arlie R. Slabaugh, 1959. (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Confederate Veteran, Volume XL, Number 11, 1932. (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - "Fort Sumter and Confederate Diplomacy," by Ludwell H. Johnson, reprinted from The Journal of Southern History, Volume XXVII, Number 4, 1960. (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - "Governor Letchner's Candid Correspondence," by F.N. Boney, reprinted from Civil War History, Volume X, Number 2, 1964. (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - "John Letchner's Secret Criticism of the Confederate," by F.N. Boney, reprinted from The Virginia Magazine of History and Biography, Volume 72, Number 3, 1964. (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - Journal of the Confederate Historical Society, Volume 1, Numbers 1-2, 1962. (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Journal of the Confederate Historical Society, Volume 1, Numbers 3-4, 1963. (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - "Lines Written for Memorial Day," by Josephine Powell Beaty, reprinted from The Historian, 1941. (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Military Affairs, (Civil War Issue), Volume XXIV, Number 2, 1960. (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Military Collector and Historian, Volume X, Numbers 3-4, and Volume XII, Number 2, 1958-1960. (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Pictorial Map Showing Historic Shrines and Battlefields of the Civil War, 1861-1865, undated. (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Reasons for the National Centennial Commemoration of the Civil War: Its Basic Objectives and Potential Values, by A.B. Moore (Alabama Civil War Centennial Commission), 1963. (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Robert E. Lee: The Beloved General, published by John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1956. (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - The Air Arm of the Confederacy: A History of Origins and Usages of War Balloons by the Southern Armies during the Civil War, by Joseph J. Cornish, III., (Official Publication 11, Richmond Civil War Centennial Committee), 1963. (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - "The American Tragedy: The Civil War in Retrospect," lecture given by Avery O. Craven and Frank E. Vandiver, 1959. (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - The Campaign and Battle of Gettysburg, by Lt. Col. Joseph B. Mitchell, 1959. (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - The Civil War: America's Tragic Years, by Audine R. Smith, undated. (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - The Civil War Horse: An Equine Saga, by Mort R. Lewis, (Official Publication 10, Richmond Civil War Centennial Committee), undated. (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - The Civil War in the Valley of History [map], undated. (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - "The First Public War, 1861-1865," address by Frank E. Vandiver, 1962. (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - The Great Locomotive Chase on the Western and Atlantic Railroad, published by the Louisville and Nashville Railroad, undated. (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - The Iron Horse Goes to War, by Bill Bunce, undated. (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - "The Lesson and the Legacy," Special Issue of Army Information Digest, Volume 16, Number 8, 1961. (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - The Military Leadership of the North and the South, by T. Harry Williams, 1960. (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - "The Raven Tamed: An 1845 Sam Houston Letter," by F.N. Boney, reprinted from The Southwestern Historical Quarterly, Volume LXVIII, Number 1, 1964. (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - The Things that Endured, published by The Lux Company, 1961. (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - The War, 1861-1865: As Depicted in Prints by Currier and Ives, published by Nationwide Mutual Insurance Company, 1960. (Box 60, Folder 22)
      - Union Worthies, Numbers 16-17, (Robert A. Toombs and Henry W. Halleck), 1961-1962. (Box 60, Folder 23)
      - Virginia Record, Volume LXXXIII, Number 1, 1961. (Box 60, Folder 24)
      - "Voices from the North," by F.N. Boney, undated. (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Naval History Publications.
      - A Brief Guide to U.S. Naval History Sources in the Washington, D.C. Area, published by the United States Navy, 1957. (Box 60, Folder 26)
      - Civil War Naval Chronology, 1861-1865, Part I, published by the United States Navy, Naval History Division, 1961. (Box 60, Folder 27)
      - "Sea Power in the Civil War," by Rear Admiral John D. Hayes, reprinted from U.S. Naval Institute Proceedings, 1961. (Box 60, Folder 28)
      - The Civil War at Sea: The Nation Notes and Long Remembers, Special Issue of NAVY: The Magazine of Sea Power, 1961. (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - The Submarine in the United States Navy, published by the United States Navy, Naval History Division, 1960. (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - The VIRGINIA No Longer Exists, by William J. Morgan, 1960. (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - United States Naval History, Naval Biography, Naval Strategy and Tactics: A Selected and Annotated Bibliography, published by the United States Navy, 1959. (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - State-Specific Publications.
      - Alabama.
        - Location and Classification and Dates of Military Events in Alabama, 1861-1865, by William Letford and Allen W. Jones, 1961. (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Connecticut.
        - The Connecticut Civil War Centennial: Connecticut Military and Naval Leaders in the Civil War, compiled by Col. E.P. Leddy and Edward J. Lonergan, undated. (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Delaware.
        - Delaware in the Civil War, edited by W. Emerson Wilson, 1962. (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Georgia.
        - Georgia Civil War Historical Markers, published by the Georgia Historical Commission, 1964. (Box 61, Folder 8)
        - Why Georgia Should Commemorate the Civil War, by Bell Irvin Wiley, undated. (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Illinois.
        - Illinois and the Civil War, by Clyde C. Walton, 1961. (Box 61, Folder 10)
        - Report of the Civil War Centennial Commission of Illinois, 1961. (Box 61, Folder 11)
        - The Illinois Central Railroad and the Civil War, by Carlton J. Corliss, undated. (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Indiana.
        - Indiana and the Civil War, published by the Indiana Civil War Centennial Commission, 1964. (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Iowa.
        - The Undying Procession: Iowa in the Civil War, compiled by Edith W. McElroy, undated. (Box 61, Folder 14)
        - Tramps and Triumphs of the Second Iowa Infantry, by John T. Bell, 1961. (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Louisiana.
        - Four Louisiana Civil War Stories, by East, Brown, Schley and Mims, 1961. (Box 61, Folder 16)
        - Louisiana Commemorates the Civil War Centennial, by T. Harry Williams, 1961. (Box 61, Folder 17)
        - The Civil War in Louisiana: A Chronology, by T. Harry Williams and A. Otis Hebert, Jr., undated. (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - Massachusetts.
        - Massachusetts in the Civil War: The Call to Arms, (Volume 1), by Thomas H. O'Connor, 1960. (Box 61, Folder 19)
        - Massachusetts in the Civil War: The Year of Trial and Testing, 1861-1862, (Volume 2), by Jordan D. Fiore, 1961. (Box 61, Folder 20)
        - Massachusetts in the Civil War: A Year of Crisis, 1862-1863, (Volume 3), by Edward W. Ellsworth, 1962. (Box 61, Folder 21)
        - Massachusetts in the Civil War: A Year of Dedication, 1863-1864, (Volume 4), by Howard T. Oedel, 1964. (Box 61, Folder 22)
      - Michigan.
        - Materials on the Civil War Recommended for Use in Schools, published by the Michigan Civil War Centennial Observance Commission, 1964. (Box 61, Folder 23)
        - Michigan and the Civil War Years, 1861-1865: A Wartime Chronicle, by George S. May, 1964. (Box 61, Folder 24)
      - Mississippi.
        - Mississippi in the War Between the States, published by the Mississippi Commission on the War Between the States, 1960. (Box 61, Folder 25)
        - Vicksburg in the War Between the States, published by the Mississippi Commission on the War Between the States, 1960. (Box 61, Folder 26)
      - New Hampshire.
        - New Hampshire and the Civil War, Volume 1, Numbers 2-3, 1963-1964. (Box 61, Folder 27)
      - New Jersey.
        - New Jersey in the Civil War and Civil War Facts, compiled by the New Jersey Civil War Centennial Commission, undated. (Box 61, Folder 28)
        - Proceedings of the Annual American History Workshop, presented by the New Jersey Civil War Centennial Commission, 1963-1964. (Box 62, Folder 1)
        - Steps in a Journey toward Understanding: Activities of the New Jersey Civil War Centennial Commission in 1961, by L. Ethan Ellis, 1963. (Box 62, Folder 2)
        - The Negro and New Jersey: A Checklist of Books, Pamphlets, Official Publications, Broadsides, and Dissertations, 1754-1964, compiled by Donald A. Sinclair, 1965. (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - New York.
        - New York State and the Civil War, Volume 1, Numbers 1-6, 1961. (Box 62, Folder 4)
        - New York State and the Civil War, Volume 1, Numbers 7-10, 1962. (Box 62, Folder 5)
        - New York State and the Civil War, Volume 2, Numbers 1-4, 1962. (Box 62, Folder 6)
        - New York State and the Civil War, Volume 2, Numbers 5-9, 1962-1963. (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - North Carolina.
        - North Carolina as a Civil War Battleground, 1861-1865, by John Gilchrist Barrett, 1960. (Box 62, Folder 8)
        - Pictures of the Civil War Period in North Carolina, by D.L. Corbitt, 1958. (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Ohio.
        - Ohio Colleges and the Civil War, by G. Wallace Chessman, 1963. (Box 62, Folder 10)
        - Ohio Handbook of the Civil War, by Robert S.Harper, 1961. (Box 62, Folder 11)
        - Ohio Troops in the Field, by Edward T. Downer, undated. (Box 62, Folder 12)
        - Ohio's Bounty System in the Civil War, by Eugene C. Murdock, 1963. (Box 62, Folder 13)
        - The Ohio Press in the Civil War, by Robert S. Harper, undated. (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Pennsylvania.
        - Pennsylvania and the Civil War: A Handbook, by Higginbotham, Hunter and Kent, 1961. (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Rhode Island.
        - Rhode Island Civil War Chronicles, published by the Rhode Island Civil War Centennial Commission, 1960. (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - South Carolina.
        - Military and Naval Operations in South Carolina, 1860-1865, compiled by Nora M. Davis, 1959. (Box 63, Folder 3)
        - South Carolina Speaks, published by the South Carolina Confederate War Centennial Commission, 1961. (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Tennessee.
        - Guide to the Civil War in Tennessee, compiled by the Tennessee Civil War Centennial Commission, 1960. (Box 63, Folder 5)
        - Heroines of the Blue and Gray, (University of Tennessee newsletter), 1960. (Box 63, Folder 6)
        - Southern Heroes, Heroines and Legends, (University of Tennessee newsletter), 1962. (Box 63, Folder 7)
        - Tennessee in the Civil War, published by the Tennessee Civil War Centennial Commission, 1962. (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Texas.
        - Texas in the Civil War: A Resume History, by Allan C. Ashcraft, 1962. (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Virginia.
        - A Brief History of New Market and Vicinity, by Arthur L. Hildreth, 1964. (Box 63, Folder 10)
        - A Brief History of the Norfolk Naval Shipyard, by Marshall W. Butt, 1959. (Box 63, Folder 11)
        - A History of the Town of Fairfax, by Jeanne J. Rust, 1960. (Box 63, Folder 12)
        - A Roster of Confederate Soldiers Buried in Stonewall Cemetery, Winchester, Virginia, compiled by Lucy F. Kurtz and Benny Ritter, 1962. (Box 63, Folder 13)
        - Automobile Tour of Principal Battlefields near Richmond, published by First and Merchants National Bank, 1961. (Box 63, Folder 14)
        - Belle Boyd: Southern Spy of the Shenandoah, by Laura V. Hale, undated. (Box 63, Folder 15)
        - Centennial Exhibition of Staunton and Augusta County During the Civil War [event program], 1961. (Box 63, Folder 16)
        - Civil War Action in Rockingham County, Virginia, undated. (Box 63, Folder 17)
        - Civil War Battles in Winchester and Frederick County, Virginia, 1861-1865, 1960. (Box 63, Folder 18)
        - Commemorative Program Marking the Centennial of the Battle of Ox Hill, Chantilly (event program), 1962. (Box 63, Folder 19)
        - Confederate History of Charles City County, Virginia, compiled by Mary R. Copland, 1957. (Box 63, Folder 20)
        - Confederate History of Culpeper County, by Mrs. Berkeley G. Calfee, undated. (Box 63, Folder 21)
        - Confederate Military Hospitals in Richmond, by Robert W. Waitt, Jr., (Official Publication 22, Richmond Civil War Centennial Commission), 1964. (Box 63, Folder 22)
        - Directory of Officials, 1861-1865: Richmond, Virginia and Confederate, compiled by Louis H. Manarin and Robert W. Waitt, Jr., (Official Publication 15, Richmond Civil War Centennial Committee), undated. (Box 63, Folder 23)
        - Fairfax County and the War Between the States, published by the Fairfax County Civil War Centennial Commission, 1961. (Box 63, Folder 24)
        - First Battle of Saltville, Virginia (event program), 1964. (Box 63, Folder 25)
        - Giles County, Virginia, 1806-1956, by Robert C. Friend, undated. (Box 63, Folder 26)
        - Henrico County Civil War Centennial Commission Annual Report, 1960. (Box 64, Folder 1)
        - Historic Guide: Richmond and James River, by Caroline R. Harrison, undated. (Box 64, Folder 2)
        - Historic Points of Interest in Richmond, Virginia, (Official Publication 24, Richmond Civil War Centennial Committee), undated. (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - Illustrated Guide to Richmond, The Confederate Capital, published by the Confederate Museum and the Valentine Museum, 1960. (Box 64, Folder 4)
        - June 1862, Civil War Battles of Harrisonburg, Virginia, by Dr. James Moore, undated. (Box 64, Folder 5)
        - Lee and Grant in Virginia: Wilderness to Appomattox [map], undated. (Box 64, Folder 6)
        - Libby Prison, (Official Publication 12, Richmond Civil War Centennial Committee), undated. (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - Louisa County and the War Between the States, 1861-1865, undated. (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - Memories in Marble: The Story of Front Royal's Four Confederate Monuments, by Laura V. Hale, 1956. (Box 64, Folder 9)
        - Military Operations in Jefferson County (Virginia and West Virginia), 1861-1865, published by authority of Jefferson County Camp, U.C.V., 1960. (Box 64, Folder 10)
        - Nelson County Civil War Soldiers, published by the Office of the Clerk, Nelson County Circuit Court, undated. (Box 64, Folder 11)
        - New Guidebook and Maps of Fredericksburg, Virginia, (Civil War Centennial Edition), 1961. (Box 64, Folder 12)
        - Orange Court House, 1861-1865, published by the Orange County Civil War Centennial Committee, undated. (Box 64, Folder 13)
        - Portsmouth under Four Flags, 1752-1961, by Marshall W. Butt, 1961. (Box 64, Folder 14)
        - Rededication Ceremony Honoring General J.E.B. Stuart on the One Hundredth Anniversary of His Mortal Wounding, Henrico County (event program), 1964. (Box 64, Folder 15)
        - Reenactment of the First Battle of Winchester [event program], 1962. (Box 64, Folder 16)
        - Richmond, Virginia, 1861-1865, by C. Hobson Goddin, (Official Publication 8, Richmond Civil War Centennial Committee), undated. (Box 64, Folder 17)
        - Seven Fateful Days of 1865: Retreat of Lee's Army of Northern Virginia from Petersburg to Appomattox, April 2-9, 1865, compiled by Wilmer R. Turner, 1961. (Box 64, Folder 18)
        - Suggested Course of Study for Centennial Anniversary of the War Between the States, 1961-1965 in Smyth County Schools, by Clara Hill Carner, undated. (Box 64, Folder 19)
        - Spotsylvania County Commemoration: Battle of Fredericksburg, reviewed by Joseph P. Cullen, 1962. (Box 64, Folder 20)
        - Surry County at War, 1861-1865, by Kathleen P. Horne, 1963. (Box 64, Folder 21)
        - The Angel of Marye's Heights, by Richard N. Lanier, 1961. (Box 64, Folder 22)
        - The Civil War in Virginia, special edition of The Commonwealth, produced by the Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 1961. (Box 64, Folder 23)
        - The Magazine of Albemarle County History, Volume 22 (Civil War Issue), 1964. (Box 64, Folder 24)
        - The Story of Germanna Descendents in Reunion at Siegen Forest, Virginia, edited by Charles Herbert Huffman, 1958. (Box 65, Folder 1)
        - The Wilson-Kautz Raid, by A.B. Cummins, 1961. (Box 65, Folder 2)
        - Treadwell Smith's Diary of the Civil War, 1859-1865, published by Civil War Centennial Committee and Berryville and Clarke County Chamber of Commerce, undated. (Box 65, Folder 3)
        - Troop Movements at the Battle of Cold Harbor, 1864, (Official Publication 21, Richmond Civil War Centennial Committee), 1964. (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Warren County Civil War Centennial Commemoration: Battle of Front Royal, published by the Warren County Civil War Centennial Commission, 1962. (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - Williamsburg in the Civil War, published by the Williamsburg Civil War Committee, undated. (Box 65, Folder 5)
        - W.R. Turner Memorial Trek, Sayler's Creek Battlefield (event program), 1961. (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Washington, D.C.
        - Civil War Centennial Map of Washington D.C., undated. (Box 65, Folder 7)
        - Commemoration Service on the One Hundredth Anniversary of the Asssassination of President Abraham Lincoln, Washington, D.C. (event program), 1965. (Box 65, Folder 8)
        - The Symbol and the Sword: Washington, D.C., 1860-1865, published by the District of Columbia Civil War Centennial Commission, 1962. (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - West Virginia.
        - Centennial Observance: John Brown Raid, Harpers Ferry, West Virginia, 1959. (Box 65, Folder 10)
        - Chronology of the Civil War in West Virginia, published by the Barbour County Historical Society, 1960. (Box 65, Folder 11)
        - First Land Battle of the Civil War, Philippi, West Virginia (event program), 1961. (Box 65, Folder 12)
        - The Battle of Corricks Ford, 1961. (Box 65, Folder 13)
        - The Beginning: Philippi, 1861, by Ruth W. Dayton, 1952. (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - United States Civil War Centennial Commission Publications.
      - Emancipation Centennial, 1962: A Brief Anthology of the Preliminary Proclamation, 1962. (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Facts about the Civil War, 1959. (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Our Women of the Sixties, by Sylvia L. Dannett and Katharine M. Jones, 1963. (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - The Civil War, by James I. Robertson, Jr., 1963. (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - The Origins of the Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities, by Allan Nevins, 1962. (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - The United States on the Eve of the Civil War, As Described in the 1860 Census, 1963. (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Virginia Civil War Commission Publications.
      - A Register of Military Events in Virginia, 1861-1865, compiled by N.E. Warinner, 1959. (Box 65, Folder 21)
      - "Centennial Year," by John Warren Cooke, reprinted from The Commonwealth, 1961. (Box 65, Folder 22)
      - "Circle 'Round the Civil War Centennial Center," by Edwin F. Gahan, reprinted from the Virginia Journal of Education, 1961. (Box 65, Folder 23)
      - Confederate Medicine, by Harry J. Warthen, 1961. (Box 65, Folder 24)
      - Iron Gate to the Confederacy: Virginia, 1861-1865, by James I. Robertson, Jr., 1961. (Box 65, Folder 25)
      - J.E.B. Stuart: Calvary Leader, 1964. (Box 65, Folder 26)
      - Selected Civil War State Historical Markers, Virginia, undated. (Box 65, Folder 27)
      - "The Centennial's Final Year," by James J. Geary, reprinted from The Commonwealth, 1965. (Box 65, Folder 28)
      - The Civil War Centennial in Virginia, Opening Day Program, 1961. (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - The Life of Stonewall Jackson, 1963. (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - The Making of a President: Jefferson Davis, 1861, by Frank E. Vandiver, undated. (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - The Whole Jackson, by Lenoir Chambers 1963. (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Virginia Joins the Confederacy: Chronology of Events, November 1860-June 1861, undated. (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Virginia's Decision: The Story of The Secession Convention of 1861, by Benjamin J. Hillman, 1964. (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Virginia's Opportunity: The Civil War Centennial, 1961-1965, undated. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Publications Files.
    - A Register of Military Events in Virginia (1861-1865), 1960-1963. (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Art Work in Commission Publications, 1959-1961. (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Brochures, 1960. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Brochures and Postcards, undated. (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Bulletins to Local Centennial Committees, 1960. (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Bulletins to Local Centennial Committees, 1961. (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Centennial Newsletter, 1962-1965. (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Center, Publications on Sale at, 1962. (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Commission Publications: Correspondence, 1962-1964. (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Commission Publications: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1966. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Commission Publications: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1966. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Cut-outs, 1961-1963. (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Jefferson, Papers of: Correspondence, 1962-1964. (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Davis, Jefferson, Papers of: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1962-1965. (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Flags of the Civil War, undated. (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Grant, Ulysses, Papers of, 1964-1966. (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Historic Clippings (mostly reprints), 1861; 1933. (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Historic Images and Prints, 1861-1864. (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Historic Manuscripts (reprints), 1861-1863. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Iron Gate to the Confederacy: Correspondence, 1959-1960. (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Iron Gate to the Confederacy: Correspondence, 1961. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Iron Gate to the Confederacy: Correspondence, 1962-1963. (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Iron Gate to the Confederacy: Miscellaneous Documentation, 1960-1963. (Box 68, Folder 1)